thecloud.net 2007-08-27

# About Us | Privacy

|  |    
---  
  
  * The Cloud History
  * Working Together
  * Investors
  * Service Providers
  * Technology Partners
  * Partners
  * Management
  * Management Team
  * Board
  * Jobs
  * Current vacancies
  * Contact Us
  * Site Owners
  * Wireless Customers
  * General Enquiries
  * Media Contact

  * Search

| 

The Cloud's Privacy Policy 

Please read our Privacy Policy carefully before using this website (“our website”). In these conditions “we”, “us” and “our” means The Cloud and “you” means the individual using our website. This Privacy Policy sets out how we comply with European Union data protection requirements. This applies to the entire website. 

We are committed to respecting your privacy. Once you choose to provide us with any information by which you can be identified, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this Privacy Policy. For your protection, we have given all appropriate notifications to the Information Commissioner under the Data Protection Act 1998. 

**How do we collect information about you?**  
We may collect personal information from you when you register to use the services provided on our website. 

**What information do we collect?  
** We may collect the following information: Your name; e-mail address; organisation name; phone numbers; technical details on your computer or access device; time and date of access; location of access Your billing information, transaction and credit card information Information regarding your personal or professional interests, demographics, experiences with the Services and contact preferences in order to provide you with further correspondence about our products and services. 

**What do we do with the information we gather?**  
We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons: Internal record keeping We may use the information to improve our products and services We may use the information to manage the security of our services Our representatives may follow up, by e-mail, or mail, to people as part of our customer care procedures From time to time, we may use your information to contact you for market research purposes. We may contact you by e-mail, or mail, unless you have registered with the appropriate Preference Service If you wish to cease receiving e-mail updates, then please e-mail us at webmaster@thecloud.net 

**E-mail marketing**   
Unless you have registered with the appropriate Preference Service, we would like to provide you by e-mail with information about new products, promotions, special offers and other information which we think you may find interesting. However, we appreciate that e-mail “spam” has become a problem in recent years. If you are a customer or you have previously asked us for information on our products, we may send you information on our range of products by e-mail, unless you have asked us not to do so. 

If the reason you have given us personal information is to receive e-mail information from us, we will continue to provide this information by e-mail unless you ask us not to do so. Otherwise, when you provide us with personal information, we will ask you whether or not you are happy for us to send you this kind of information by e-mail. 

If you decide at any time that you no longer wish to receive marketing e-mails from us, please contact:   
Data Protection Compliance Officer   
54-58 Bartholomew Close  
London EC1A 7RY  
or: webmaster@thecloud.net 

What if you think we have incorrect information or you would like a copy of the information we hold about you? We will provide details of any personal information held about you upon request. A small fee will be payable. If you would like a copy of the information held on you please write to:   
Data Protection Compliance Officer   
3rd Floor, 16-19 Gresse Street   
London W1T 1QL   
or: webmaster@thecloud.netData Protection Compliance Officer   
54-58 Bartholomew Close  
London EC1A 7RY  
or: webmaster@thecloud.net 

If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please e-mail us as soon as possible at webmaster@thecloud.net. We will correct or update any information which is found to be incorrect as soon as possible. 

**Who We Share the Information With And Your Choices**   
When you use this website and have not advised us to the contrary, you are agreeing that we may use your personal information for the purposes set out in this statement. We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties other than our subsidiaries, parent company, subsidiary of our parent company, or a purchaser or potential purchaser of our business unless we have your permission or are required by law. 

This process may include sending personal information outside of the European Economic Area and, if necessary, across international borders. The data protection laws in these countries may not be as extensive as in the European Economic Area. However, we have taken appropriate steps to ensure the same level of protection for the processing carried out in these countries as within the European Economic Area. 

**Other Websites**   
Our website may contain links to enable you to visit other web sites of interest easily. We do not have any control over that other web site. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such websites and such websites are not governed by this Privacy Policy. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement or policy applicable to the web site in question. 

**How We Use Cookies**   
We use cookies for certain areas of our website. Cookies are files that store information on your hard drive or browser that means that our website can recognise that you have visited our website before. They make it easier for you to maintain your preferences on the website, and by seeing how you use the website, we can tailor the website around your preferences and measure usability of the website. You can, should you choose, disable the cookies from your browser and delete all cookies currently stored on your computer. On Microsoft Internet Explorer, this can be done by selecting “Tools/Internet Options” and reviewing your privacy settings or selecting “delete cookies”. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website. You can find out how to do this for your particular browser by clicking "help" on your browser's menu or by visiting http://www.allaboutcookies.org/manage-cookies/index.html 

|  |  | 

|   
---  
|  | 

AT&T expands Wi-Fi access  
Agreement with The Cloud adds over 9,000 Wi-Fi locations across Europe; Delivers Immediate Benefit for Business Customers   
MORE

Mobile VoIP Receives a Major Boost Across Europe  
Agreement between Vyke and The Cloud gives mobile VoIP users pan-European access    
MORE

Inspired gaming group signs exclusive services agreement with The Cloud  
Inspired Gaming Group plc (“Inspired”), the leading worldwide player in the Open Server-Based Gaming (Open SBG™) market, and The Cloud Limited ("The Cloud"), a leading wireless broadband provider, today announced that they have signed a seven year exclusive Services Agreement for Inspired  to provide Network Services to The Cloud.   
MORE

The Cloud switches on Europe’s most advanced WiFi network across the City of London  
Nokia offers 350,000 people free access to the City of London network   
MORE

The Cloud and Future Publishing to offer exclusive content for PSP over public WiFi  
The Cloud announces PSP WiFi package with seamless internet access and targeted content for gamers    
MORE

The Cloud's Owen Geddes on why public Wi-Fi isn't just for suits   
TECHDIGEST - Wi-Fi hotspots are mainly useful for business types, right? Great for catching up with emails over a Latte or seven, while barking out PowerCommands in a series of VoIP calls with your minions. But thanks to the pricing, not that useful to those of us who don't have a company credit card. That could be changing though. [ read ]   
MORE

Vista users get free Wi-FI  
The Register - Users making the leap to Microsoft's latest OS will get a few months' free Wi-Fi usage courtesy of hotspot aggregator The Cloud. [ read ]   
MORE

Free Wi-Fi for Windows Vista Users   
ISP Review - Following on from last weeks news, The Cloud has finally added a page to its website where legitimate owners of Microsoft's new operating system (Vista) can get their free Wi-Fi Hotspot access. [ read ]   
MORE

The Cloud confirms free Wi-Fi for Vista adopters  
ISP Review - The Cloud has confirmed our earlier report, which revealed their intention to offer early adopts of Microsoft's new operating system (Vista) "free" Wi-Fi Hotspot access. [ read ]   
MORE

The Cloud has silver lining for Vista users   
Computeractive.co.uk - Hotspot provider The Cloud is offering UK Vista customers up to three months of free Wifi access.[ read ]   
MORE

Vista early birds can catch The Cloud free   
Silicon.com - Early adopters of Windows Vista will be able to get three months' free wi-fi access with hotspot operator The Cloud. [ read ]   
MORE

Channel 4 podcasts available via Wi-Fi  
WebUser   
MORE

Birmingham's Bullring Centre gets WiFi  
ERT Weekly.com  \- The Bullring shopping centre in Birmingham has cemented its position as one of the world’s most advanced retail complexes by offering its visitors wireless Internet access. [ read ]   
MORE

The Cloud brings WiFi to shoppers  
Computeractive.co.uk  \- Wireless access to be available throughout Birmingham’s biggest shopping centre.[ read ]   
MORE

Tablet works faster, lasts longer  
IT Week - Dan Robinson   
MORE

Visionary making London wireless  
City AM - Joanne McCulloch - George Polk, founder of WiFi company The Cloud is the winner of our search for the most innovative business person in the Square Mile   
MORE

Wireless security  
NMA Explains - Ross Bentley - The nature of a wireless connection makes it more prone to external access, but that doesn't mean it can't be secured.   
MORE

Channel 4  
Marketing - Channel 4 is making its podcast content available over a public Wi-Fi network for a two-month period.   
MORE

The Cloud looks to reign over TV  
Whatpc.co.uk  \- An increasing number of consumers are turning to handheld gadgets to get news and other video content, according to Wifi and network operator The Cloud.[ read ]   
MORE

The Cloud looks to reign over TV  
Computeractive.co.uk  \- An increasing number of consumers are turning to handheld gadgets to get news and other video content, according to Wifi and network operator The Cloud.[ read ]   
MORE

|   
---|---|---  
  
Having access to The Cloud’s network helps reinforce The British Library’s image as a progressive, technologically aware organisation and we are excited to see how usage will evolve

British Library  
  
|   
---  
|  |  Address  
  
City  
  
State / Province  
  
Zip Code / Post Code  
  
Country  
  
Distance Radius (Miles)  
  
---|---
